

NICOLE NAM

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a web developer who brings 7+ years of experience in the culinary, hospitality, and the art industry to the table, as well as recent experience developing dynamic web applications focused on the user experience, As a team player, I believe in a positive learning environment and that celebrating small wins helps you to stay motivated through your journey. My top skills include Creativity, Collaboration, Problem Solving.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- HTML/CSS
- SASS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- Git
 - REST Api
 - Bootstrap
- Adobe XD
- Responsive Design Vue js

CONTACT INFORMATION

(647)-404-9660 nicolenam.work@gmail.com Portfolio: https://nicole-<u>nam.github.io/nicole-portfolio/</u>

LANGUAGES

English Korean

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

XTM Inc. March 2021 - Present

XTM is a Toronto Fintech company, global card issuer, payment specialist, and marketing solutions company. Created reusable components for the web application products using Vue js, Bootstrap Vue. Experience working with RESTful APIs, JSON, integrating internal Apis.

Banquet Cook

Ritz Carlton Hotel | Nov 2016 to Dec 2019

Developed, strong organizational, and time management skills in order to boost productivity under pressure. Worked effectively with all team members to promote a positive working environment. Created, and prepared new and enticing menu items for the VIP lounge guests. Managed allergies with care and professionalism for guests' safety and satisfaction.

Banquet Cook

Four Seasons Hotel | Sept 2015 to Nov 2016

Practiced the ability to handle multiple preparations and tasks simultaneously while maintaining 5-star quality. Demonstrated strong working knowledge of basic cooking and effective preparation methods. Prepared over 400 individual meal proportions, daily, while managing and training student/kitchen personnel.

EDUCATION

Web Development Professional

Red Academy | Jan 2020 to Mar 2020

Culinary Management

George Brown College | Jan 2014 to sep 2015

Theatre Acting BA

Dongguk Univ. Korea | mar 2005 to jun 2009

PROJECTS

Tip Calculator App VUE JS | HTML | CSS

This is a tip calculator web app built with Vue js. Enter your meal cost with the tip percentage, and split the cost among your company.

Contact Directory Form

VUE JS | HTML | CSS

This is a contact directory, which the user can add, delete their contact information and toggle the details.